Register of the Ernest W. Lefever Papers, 1933-2007
Hoover Institution Archives
- ETHICS AND PUBLIC POLICY CENTER, 1974-1987
  - Publications
    - Printed material
      - Herz, Martin F., The Prestige Press and the Christmas Bombing, 1972: Images and Reality in Viet Nam, 1980. Edited transcript and printed copy (Folder 3)
      - Griffith, Carol F. (ed.), Christianity and Politics: Catholic and Protestant Perspectives, 1981. Edited transcript and printed copy (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Hessen, Robert (ed.), Does Big Business Rule America? 1981. Edited transcript and printed copy (Folder 2)
      - Ramsey, James B., The Oil Muddle: Control vs. Competition, 1981. Edited transcript and printed copy (Folder 3)
      - Seabury, Paul, America's Stake in the Pacific, 1981. Edited transcript and printed copy (Folder 4)
      - Friedman, Murray, The Utopian Dilemma: American Judaism and Public Policy, 1985. Typescript (Box 37, Folder 1-4)
  - Increment, 1989 June. Correspondence, writings, reports, minutes, appointment books, calendars, and printed matter, relating to the Ethics and Public Policy Center and its conferences or reports on the PLO, Taiwan, and the World Council of Churches (Box 38-41)
  - Increment, 1989 Dec. Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, conference material, press releases, typescripts, printed reports, notes, and printed material. Includes material relating to nuclear weapons, religion, Russia, Cambodia, Africa, and the Ethics and Public Policy Center, 1949-1989 (Box 43-53)
  - Increment, 1990 Dec. Correspondence, typescripts, press releases, and printed material, 1979-1989. Relates to evangelism in America (Box 54)
  - Increment, 1991 July. Correspondence, writings, memoranda, reports, class notes, and videotapes, 1937-1990. Relates to the Ethics and Public Policy Center, religious studies and ethics, and American pacifism during World War II, including the rehabilitation of German prisoners of war in Europe (Box 58-66)
- INCREMENTS (Box 58-173)
- DECLASSIFIED RECORD, 1970 (Box 173)
  - 2011 September release of record, 1970 January 13 (Box 173)
    Lefever lecture, "Role of the Indigenous Military in Developing Countries," U.S. Army War College
- PHOTOGRAPHS
  See photo card file.